adultmatchmaker.com.au 2019-03-12

# Privacy | Adult Match Maker

## Introduction

This statement includes:

  * our collection statement, explaining aspects of our collection and use of personal information
  * our privacy policy, further explaining how we manage personal information.

## Collection Statement

### Who we are

Giga Pty Ltd ABN 68 079 638 547

### Our contact details

  * PO BOX 1026, North Sydney, NSW 2059
  * Email: [support@giga.com.au](mailto:support@giga.com.au "support@giga.com.au")

### Collection from third party sources

We may collect personal information from someone other than you, and you may not be aware of the collection, when it is not reasonable or practicable to collect it from you, and it is available from:

  * publicly available sources
  * other companies in our group that you may have dealt with
  * third parties like our business partners, your authorised representative/s
  * fraud checking agencies
  * our websites and how you use them (through the use of cookies)
  * various parties listed under Disclosing personal information in our Privacy Policy.

### Collection under law

We may be required to collect personal information in order to comply with the law.

### Why we collect and hold personal information

We collect and hold personal information because:

  * we may need to use it to operate our business
  * we may need it to assist to facilitate and optimise your experience of using the site.

The uses and disclosures we may make of personal information are detailed in our Privacy Policy.

### Unavailability of personal information

If we cannot collect the information we need about you, we may not be able to supply the products or services you want.

### Disclosing personal information

We may disclose personal information as reasonably required to contractors and suppliers whose goods and services that we use to operate our business and provide products and support to you, to comply with our contractual obligations with regulatory authorities, and to other parties detailed in our Privacy Policy.

### Access and correction

Our privacy policy contains information about how you can access and seek correction of the personal information about you that we hold.

### Complaints

Our privacy policy explains how you can complain about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles, and how we will deal with such a complaint.

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Personal information

This refers to information or an opinion about a living person who is identified or reasonably identifiable, whether or not true and whether or not recorded in material form.

### Kinds of personal information we collect and hold

Broadly, we may collect and hold:

  * personal details like date of birth, gender, photographs of you, driver's licence information, passport information (and other identification) and occupation
  * contact details like email addresses and phone numbers
  * financial details like credit card numbers and your billing and payment history with us
  * service-related details like your user name, encrypted password and service usage history, support incidents, data from cookies, enquiries and complaints
  * other details relating to special situations.

In any case, we only collect personal information that is reasonably necessary to support our functions and activities. If we cannot collect the information we need about you, we may not be able to supply the products or service you want, or may not be able to give you the full functionality of our services.

### Collecting personal information

Unless it is not reasonable or practicable to do so, and in other cases allowed by law, we will collect personal information about you directly from you (eg when you contact us by phone or online, or apply for membership of our websites, or services on our website).

In other cases, we may collect personal information about you from:

  * publicly available sources
  * other companies in our group that you may have dealt with
  * third parties like our business partners, your authorised representative/s
  * fraud checking agencies
  * our websites and how you use them (through the use of cookies and through the use of third party tracking tools such as Google Analytics)
  * various parties listed under Disclosing personal information below.

### Holding personal information

We hold personal information in soft copy at our offices and in other facilities that we own or license from third parties, like data centres. We take reasonable steps to keep it secure and to protect it from unauthorised access, use or alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorisation controls.

### Why we collect and hold personal information

We collect and hold personal information because:

  * we may need to use it to operate our business
  * we may need it to assist, facilitate and optimise your experience of using the site

### Using personal information

We may use personal information:

  * to identify you and verify your age
  * to prevent fraud
  * to supply products (including goods and/or services) to you
  * to give you information about us and our products, and product offers
  * for direct marketing – see Direct marketing for details
  * to improve our products, our marketing and our website
  * to answer your enquiries
  * to give you customer support and service
  * to better understand your needs and respond to them
  * to manage and plan our products and business
  * to charge and bill you for products you use
  * to collect payment from you or make payment to you
  * to monitor, manage, test and improve our network and facilities
  * to comply with various laws or contractual obligations that apply to us
  * for other purposes related to the operation of our business.

### Disclosing personal information

We may disclose personal information as reasonably required to contractors and suppliers who supply or support us in:

  * market research, sales and marketing
  * direct marketing – see Direct marketing for details
  * identity and fraud checking
  * billing
  * legal and regulatory advice and compliance
  * risk management
  * otherwise providing goods and services that we use to operate our business and provide services and support to you
  * to your authorised representative/s
  * if you ask us to do so
  * to our agents, and members of our corporate group
  * to persons who invest in or acquire all or part of our business or company, or are considering doing so
  * to Government authorities where reasonably required by law or as otherwise permitted by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).

### Direct marketing

We may use and disclose personal information to direct market to you products or services offered by us, our agents, affiliates and members of our corporate group, where we think the offers will be of interest to you, using:

  * email
  * electronic messaging
  * social media
  * targeted web content
  * other direct marketing channels.

Direct marketing may continue until you opt-out by using our online facility or advising our customer support to do so.

### Accessing and correcting personal information

You may access and correct your own personal information. Please contact us for these purposes using the details in Contacting us below. We shall process and respond to your request in accordance with Australian Privacy Principle 12. There is no charge for making a request but a reasonable administrative charge, on a cost recovery basis, may be payable before we agree to provide access.

### Complaints

If you wish to complain about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles, please contact us using the details in Contacting us below. We shall:

  * acknowledge your complaint within a reasonable time
  * give you an estimated first response time
  * allocate your complaint to a suitably senior staff member
  * process and respond to your complaint as soon as we reasonably can.

### Cookies

  * We use cookies to collect usage and preference information on our website. We also use Google Analytics (a) Display Advertising – Remarketing; and (b) Demographics and Interest Reporting. Further information about opting out is available here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Data collected by cookies is disclosed to Google Inc who is based overseas including in the USA.
  * We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, may show ads on sites across the Internet.
  * We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.
  * We use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics.
  * For furhter information on how we use cookies, please refere to our Cookie Policy.

### Your rights and your preferences (GDPR Update): 

A new European Union law, called the General Data Protection Regulation or "GDPR" affords certain rights to individuals in relation to their personal data. We have implemented additional transparency and access controls in our Privacy Statement, Account settings and Contact methods to help users take advantage of those rights. As available and except as limited under applicable law, the rights afforded to individuals are:

**Right of access** \- the right to be informed of and request access to the personal data we process about you;

**Right to rectification** \- the right to request that we amend or update your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete;

**Right to erasure** \- the right to request that we delete your personal data;

**Right to restrict** \- the right to request that we temporarily or permanently stop processing all or some of your personal data;

**Right to object** \- the right, at any time, to object to us processing your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation; the right to object to your personal data being processed for direct marketing purposes;

**Right to data** \- the right to request a copy of your personal data in electronic format; and

**Right not to be subject to automated decision-making** \- the right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated decision making, including profiling, where the decision would have a legal effect on you or produce a similarly significant effect.

In order to enable you to exercise these rights in relation to how Adult Match Maker uses your personal data, we encourage you to read our Privacy Statement & Cookie Policy.

To record, make known, or change your preferences we offer the following options:

Account settings - General Account Settings, Privacy & Blocking Settings, Notifications & Communication settings - allow you to choose which communications you receive from us and from other users, Take a break or Terminate account settings;

### Contacting us

Questions, requests and complaints regarding our Privacy Statement or our compliance with privacy laws should be directed to us by “ContactUs” page on the website or email to support@giga.com.au, or by post.

**The Privacy Officer**  
PO BOX 1026, North Sydney, NSW 2059
